<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flags on BitsForEveryone</title>
    <link>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flags on BitsForEveryone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 14:14:20 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Level Four</title>
      <link>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/army_hacker_team_got_root/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 03:13:37 -1337</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/army_hacker_team_got_root/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Thanks for your interest in the USMA Cadet Competitive Cyber Team
Flag Four army_hacker_team_got_root: Wow, you found the final flag. Well done. In cybersecurity competitions called capture-the-flag, aspring or full fledge hackers attempt to recover strings of characters called flags. These flags represent critical data that is intended to be protected by the system. It could be passwords, credit card numbers, social security numbers, or even the full schematics of a DS-1 Orbital Battle Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Level One</title>
      <link>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/p0st3r_o_awe50m3nezz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 03:13:37 -1337</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/p0st3r_o_awe50m3nezz/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Thanks for your interest in the USMA Cadet Competitive Cyber Team
Flag One: p0st3r_o_awe50m3nezz Whoah, first flag found. Well done. In cybersecurity competitions called capture-the-flag, aspring or full fledge hackers attempt to recover strings of characters called flags. These flags represent critical data that is intended to be protected by the system. It could be passwords, credit card numbers, social security numbers, or even the full schematics of a DS-1 Orbital Battle Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Level Three</title>
      <link>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/morsecodefasterthantexting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 03:13:37 -1337</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/morsecodefasterthantexting/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Thanks for your interest in the USMA Cadet Competitive Cyber Team
Flag Three: morsecodefasterthantexting Wow, you found the third flag, only one more to go. Well done. In cybersecurity competitions called capture-the-flag, aspring or full fledge hackers attempt to recover strings of characters called flags. These flags represent critical data that is intended to be protected by the system. It could be passwords, credit card numbers, social security numbers, or even the full schematics of a DS-1 Orbital Battle Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Level Two</title>
      <link>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/go_army_cyber_hack_everyonez/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 03:13:37 -1337</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/go_army_cyber_hack_everyonez/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Thanks for your interest in the USMA Cadet Competitive Cyber Team
Flag Two: go_army_cyber_hack_everyonez Wow, you found the second flag. Well done. In cybersecurity competitions called capture-the-flag, aspring or full fledge hackers attempt to recover strings of characters called flags. These flags represent critical data that is intended to be protected by the system. It could be passwords, credit card numbers, social security numbers, or even the full schematics of a DS-1 Orbital Battle Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flag Level Zero</title>
      <link>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/flag_i_found/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 03:13:37 -1337</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bitsforeveryone.com/flags/flag_i_found/</guid>
      <description>What are you doing? You don&amp;rsquo;t follow instructions very well do you.
Flag Zero: flag_i_found I told you that was not a real flag, but no you had to go and try it out. Well at least you read and sort of followed directions.
Here is your consolation prize!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>